// Questions 
// 1. What pet does Cartman Have?
// a. Gerbil b. Fish c. Cat* d. Dog

// 2. what character did Issac Hayes play on on the show?
// a. Randy b. Chef* c. the mayor d. Mr. Mackey\

// 3. Which of the following celebrities have not been in South Park?
// a. Tom Hanks* b. Russell Crowe c.Mark Zuckerberg d. Kanye West

// 4. Which character wants to be a stand up comedian?
// a. Token b. Stan c. Butters d. Jimmy*

// 5. Which character is a Geologist?
// a. Gerald Broflofski b.Randy Marsh* c. Mr. Garrison d.Jimbo

// 6. According to South Park, what music gets rid of hippies?
// a. Pop b. Country c.Metal* d. Rap

// 7. What was Jesus's talk show called?
// a.Talk Jesus b. Jesus and friends c. Jesus and pals* d. Jesus live

// 8. In the episode 'Cartmanland', why does Cartman hate theme parks?
// a. Not enough extreme rides b.He's afaraid of rides c. He had an accident at a theme park when he was young d. too many lines*

// 9. What is Butter's first name?
// a. Leopold* b.Luke c. David d. Josh

// 10. In the episode 'Smug Alert', what does Kyle's father obsess over?
// a. Hybrid cars* b. Pickup Trucks c. SUVs d. Sedans

const myQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'what pet does Cartman have?',
        answers: {
            A: 'Gerbil',
            B: 'Fish',
            C: 'Cat', 
            D: 'Dog'
        },
        answer: 'C'
    }

    {
        question: 'What character did Issac Hayes play on on the show?',
        answers: {
            A: 'Randy Marsh',
            B: 'Chef',
            C: 'The mayor', 
            D: 'Mr. Mackey'
        },
        answer: 'B'
    }

    {
        question: 'Which one of the following celebrities have not been impersonated on South Park?',
        answers: {
            A: 'Tom Hanks',
            B: 'Russell Crowe',
            C: 'Mark Zuckerberg', 
            D: 'Kanye West'
        },
        answer: 'A'
    }

    {
        question: 'Which character wants to be a stand up comedian?',
        answers: {
            A: 'Token',
            B: 'Butters',
            C: 'Stan', 
            D: 'Jimmy'
        },
        answer: 'D'
    }

    {
        question: 'Which character is a Geologist?',
        answers: {
            A: 'Gerald Broflofski',
            B: 'Randy Marsh',
            C: 'Mr. Garrison', 
            D: 'Jimbo'
        },
        answer: 'B'
    }

    {
        question: 'According to South Park what kind of music gets rid of hippes',
        answers: {
            A: 'Pop',
            B: 'Country',
            C: 'Metal', 
            D: 'Rap'
        },
        answer: 'C'
    }

    {
        question: 'Jesus had a talk show called?',
        answers: {
            A: 'Talk Jesus',
            B: 'Jesus and Friends',
            C: 'Jesus and Pals', 
            D: 'Jesus Live'
        },
        answer: 'C'
    }

    {
        question: 'In the episode "Cartman Land" why does Cartman hate theme parks?',
        answers: {
            A: 'Not enough extreme rides',
            B: 'He is afraid of rides',
            C: 'He had an accident at a theme park when he was young', 
            D: 'Too many lines'
        },
        answer: 'D'
    }

    {
        question: 'What is Butters first name?',
        answers: {
            A: 'Leopold',
            B: 'Clyde',
            C: 'Stan', 
            D: 'Kyle'
        },
        answer: 'A'
    }

    {
        question: 'In the episode "Smug Alert" what does Gerald Broflofski obsess over?',
        answers: {
            A: 'Hybrid cars',
            B: 'Pickup trucks',
            C: 'SUVs', 
            D: 'Sedans'
        },
        answer: 'A'
    }
]
